Live tension free after download this application Half time for charging double time for using
Nice app Very good app download now
Fantastic Excellent
Useful app loved it
5 times excellent said,ok!!! Excellent app to have battry optimization with usefull safe save the battery.... Excellent excellent outstanding app total 5 stars
& gamd
Super app... Really awsome...
loved it thank
Good apps
Good Battery saver app that does what it's supposed to do.
Cool
Very usefull
Cool and nice app worth download for
Excellent Works really well.
💪👍APP Great app really works highly recommend
Great app Works well and helps me deal with the latest Android load which is a power hog.
F.a.b It tells you what your percentage is and closes down you apps to saving your battery
Nice app
Its wonderful Its very useful and safe
Strong Cool
Hoho Great apps. Helps me a lot!!
Cool
It very good app that every body shuold use
Awesome
super I love this apps so much
Nice app
Realy gud it helps me a lot.
Hi Good app love it
Vrary fast Ve
I like it Good application.
Amazing you should 100% get this
Good job Works just as described
بهترین
hi ok
Must have Very very good
Great Great app
Super
Uugu Buvuvu
It's an amazing app It reduces my tension about My battery discharge.
It really works
Works wonderfully.
Loved it
Gr8 app.. Makes a huge impact on your phone and works great....
battery savior I love it
Sai Nice app dudes and girls
DU BATTERY& WIDGETS Awesome application tool to have on your mobile.
Helpful
Ok
Saves battery life!
Amazing Iloveit
Nice Good
Nice one
Vasanth Nice
Good Very good
Superb performance
Thanks for your app Thanks for the app
***** Good
Nice
good :D
V.gopd Keep It up
Good Kingster bee gh says the best
Excellent Awesome app
Wow:::::::::::9Iç app::::::::: Very GooooooD ........ Five star *****::::::
Good
Wonderful app
Nice apps Good
Irfhan.d. Very fine saving at least 35℅extra stand by.Lot of Thanks to developer.
Mrs Paula Calitz Love the battery saver, it helps a lot.
Good It is an awesome app .. Saves me from running outta batt from my long daily sched.....
Very good app
It really helps I love it
Nice Mohit
Perfect application There's nothing I can expect than this.
Great apps Cool
حلو حلو
Very nice Thank you
Its ok This app z such good
Du battery saver Good function. Good personalized keys
Good app!
This app is realy works at ur charging probs
Feature rich and simple.. Feature rich and simple..
Allll Love it
Excellent Excelllent .
Very good
So far so good
Perfect Perfect
Very good app
awesome
Nice job I like this
Aslam khan Aslam khan
Good
Du battery saver Good
Power It. Rock
It's a good quality and performance
Micromax A111 Its a nice apps thanks du battery saver team
Safe battery Very good ..
Note 3 Goo app
Great Tnx
Cool!
. Excellent job
Wow Love this app
Big G Wonderful application I was saying a good thing to have on your phone you will love this application thank you
Excellent app. &lt;3
Hey u guys should make it an anti virus too
Aah Super
Super Superb application
Samsung gal s5 Works very well on my droid.
I hope I wil wrk on sony
its good gsj
Love it plz download
Love it at all I like this apps
Love it Great!!!!!!
Super Wow
Smart siva Suppppppppper apps
Very good (y)
Wow I LIKE THIS APP..
me im liking this app.. ive tried other apps but its one more amazing
(Y)
I really like this app Best result compare to others battery savers app
Good
Chibuzor I give it a 5
Nice cooldown it work 👍
Great app Loved the app
This app isssss AMAZING!!!!!!!!!!!
The best
Ta Da
Really useful app. Definitely a must if your android phone drains battery fast like mine.
Like it It lives in me
.. Great
Loved it It really works.great application
Good app
Jjhhhjn Jisa naam wisa kam
Fantastic
Loved this app...
Sooraj
coool its very cool and useful
DU Battery saver This type is 100% perfect
I potli patkalu Awesome
nice
It's good A very good app for people having mobiles with low battery life.
Awsome
Its working
Nice! Good job!
Excellent & Accurate app
Nice app Try it
Good
this is so awesome
Excellent I like that it keeps me up-dated
Very nice
Great Seriously helps save battery amd gives money on sas3
This is the chutiya app
Amazing This app is great i have a Samsung galaxy s3 and it saves my battery alot! Thanks!!!
Good
Nice
I like it a lot haha♡♡♡
Works very well ! 5 of 5
Like
Awesome Fantasyic
3 months I have uses3 du battery saver
Helps alot
This app is awsome A very useful app. Don't ever say no to it
Comment Super good :))
Thia app Not bd
Excellent Love it
Good
Excellent May seem counter productive to download an app to modify other apps decreasing battery life. But this really works!
Very good app
I highly sugest that every 1 should have Its the only batter saver I would ever use it s the best app out their
Supreme Excellent
Awesome So time con consuming
increased my battery time very good
Awesome Good app
Best app
Really good app
I love it (squeal) I love it
It really works...
Hmm Lets see
Du battery saver Very good
Thanks It really usefull
Good
Love it! Love it!
Barrett saver I love it
Excellent
A...May...Zing!!!! Its an awesome app. Helps me to monitor my battery usage very well. Kudos to the makers!! :)
Experience Excellent
A true battery saver! There is nothing more that needs to be said, this is the best app that I have found!
It is saver than before Long lasting battery life - samsung tab3 7"
Nice
Ok
Just awesum app... ..
Very good app Helps to save battery
nice very
nice app
Good Amazing
Good app ...
Work
Galaxy Note 3 Good apps...
Anil Its good
Good
sanjY great app it is soooooooooooooooo good thank q to whom that this app gifted to us
Its very useful I got so many benefits using this app. I was new to android. Got new s4 and installed this app. Found it very useful.
Dr battery saver The best battery saver on the market.
Its useful,,,download it now,,,amizing app,,,
Nice app Save battery life more....
Cool app Nice!
Very Good
love it yes its good
Good app to customize according to our choice..
Grrt Lovely
Great
Gd... One of the best battery saving app..
Like it. It's so nice & good. Thanks.
Love it works great
Very good
Lovin it! I absolutely love this app. 5 stars from me!
Super Good app
good happy monent ..any time online
Excellent So far all du products I've used are amazing
love it i use thiss app on both samsung phone.. and it works so good.
Super Very gd
5 stars After full battery play game or downloads files
good it is nice but sometimes it donot show battery temperature
Works great
better than Battery Doctor I made a test. This is better than battery doctor, A must have battery saver and i love the design.
I love it
Venir D m kz mabantayan ung battery
Love it
Good apps Awesome
Love Respect
Bhut acha hai y app
അടിപൊളി
Ucu
Good
DU Battery Saver
I like
Works great Saves me time and batteries.
Battery life Long lasting
excellent app it really works
good
Super
Nice! Very helpful and versatile.
Awesome Always useful
I like !! Helpful app.
Awesome Realy love it......thanks for making it
Good
Yeah! This app is so cool
Nice App Nice App!
Nice! It really works!
Awesome app! I am thoroughly impressed!!
I highly sugest that every 1 should have Its the only batter saver I would ever use it s the best app out their
Good Good
Excellent Very nice
Loving it!
nice one
Good app
Nice Love
Amazing app Cant believe it actually works!! Strongly recommended APP for all smartphone users.
Good Nice
This is a good app It makes my phone alesta!
Very nice app pls uploads and save the bettery power
Good work Like a little aap s.
good
Awesome Cool
Good
Awsome Its a good optimizing app 4 saving power
Lil nice loved Nice
Aplikasi yang sangat berguna bro
Best I use it and its working well
Great Great app. Helped me to save battery
Çok iyi . Kullanin
Excellent I try this aap. Yes this aap really worked and save battery. So i give 5 star this aap.
Excellent help Super love it!
Du Battery saver.... Good app for saving battery 's life....
FUCK U
Tamam...
Es la mejor app que uso
Awsme Its very easy too use
Great Awesome app I love it
Love it
Cool First my cellphone is too fast to lowbattery now i download it and is to fast to charge wow
Good app This app is very helpful not for saving battery but for helping to save it.
Works like a champ No problems, of course my tablet rocks! Very easy and intuitive app. Thnx
Is cool You know wat I say ha ha ha
Indeed it is good
It's a absolute must Has saved me many many times when phone should have died
get it now..!! excellent app, battery lasting alot longer now, It's a must..!!
Deserves 5 stars. Very good.
Nice Excellent
Nice Good
Thanks Tia My aunt recommend this app to me when I got my phone so thanks!! This actually works and saves 80% of my battery every day!!! -Sierra
Good App
It saved 23 minutes
Great apps...
waw good
Very Good App I really enjoyed it.
Uh Me
Suri Exelent work
excellent
Oķ super Its use full.....
I love itt
LOVE IT This app is awsome its reallyncool my battery weennttt uuuppp!!!!!;)
5 starts Awesome app!!
Goog Good
Best of the best saves you battery till next change.
Excellent! Does what it says, saves battery.
Awesome!! Low Battery?? Better Get This!
thank love
Awesome
Thanks I've gone for day's without having to charge thanks
Hi I think it's very nice application
Aa Good
Great battery saver Best evr.
Booost Ia secret
great app for ur's consumption control.
Excellent Excellent
Nice
Love it This amazing apps make my phone more last longer than ever
سینا عالیه دان کنید
Nice app
عالیه
good signal
Par excellennt Pcn odissa.
Samsung note 3 Very nice & use full application
Pure Gold! Awesome App!! Two years later and it's still gold.
get it now..!! excellent app, battery lasting alot longer now, It's a must..!!
Very nice and good app
So helpful Definate 5 stars
Great app for me after for long year im used smart phone!!
Saved time Saved 1 hour already
Good Good
Energy saved You can control your power usage during travelling. Excellentt
Grand Go 4 It...!!!
Pretty darn good
Saver Very good app
The BEST Nice and awesome app where it keeps my battery safe.....
Good
Good Good
Saving charge
Good app This app helped my phone a lot. Im looking forward for more updates and better features in the future.
My Battery
Nice
Cool Cool
Awesome It's working but lately
Great app
Great Actually saved my battery and gave me longer power
Goods App very well with the same thing. ..
Goood Best..
Nice suggestions
Dose a great job!!! Helps to keep your phone battery life, last longer...
siki nice aap
Love it
Gret on galaxy Tab.2 Goof aplication, am very happy
Nice app good lasting battery long life
Excellent Love this app
Best The best sofware
Love it
Awesome
Samsung galaxy grand Nice
Great Application This app does what it's supposed to do. Give it a tree.
Try Get
Best power saver It is the best power saver I have tried. Just don't download all the other apps that pop up.
It's the best battery saver app i hav ever used....
Good app Very useful app.
Great app It works well on my Samsung Galaxy S4 mini
Best apps its very helpfull
Cool app
V good V good
Great Does what I need no complaints so far!
Star Nice application
It saved 23 minutes
N.... Nic......
Distinction Very good
Love
Very good applications
Thor Thorbaik
Excellent Mind blowing
Gud NYC app
Loving it Because my battery drains slower because of this :-)
King ♔ Good 1
its good app yar ala,kus k dhakan esi chezain pta ni kesy bna laity hain.
Du battery saver I love it
Cool Nice app
Woooow
New M9, HTC, Helped, considerable...
Mahes Super
Great Great resourceful app
I like it Its cool
Gooooood.
Nice
the best i love it it is amazing
The best app ever and good
Good Class
Crappy phone This helps keep it running as best it can and saves my battery a lot
Great app! Only just installed this app & already saved 110 minutes! Incredible.
Love It
So nice app Good job guys.
Excellent Super app I like that
REALLY GOOD I love it. When my phone is almost dead, It comes im and saves the day
Awesome!
Mast Good
Best thing ever Best thing to do in small time
Raviprakash V.v.v. Gud
...nice app...
Cool stuff
Great!! This app is nice.. It helps.
Very good
I like this app.
XD OMG this really helps and I'm a gamer and I watch video's. On my phone and it really keeps my battery alive longer then what I'm use to
Cool Good
JATT Fuddu app dload nai hndi
Cool It is ok
Good Love
Great I like this apps
Works
Loved it
Great
Amazing my phone was its at 0% and I'm still been using it for the past 10 minutes
Nice Good job
Good app Good battery long lasting app...to have this app is a good one...
dubatterry
Top Wow
Nice
Excellent Good job! I feel my smartphone always fresh!
Great app Live this app
Good Nice!
Excellent Excellent
Very very fast
Cool
My battery last lots longer! My battery kept running out to fast a lot of app's I didn't need or want on turned themselves on and drained the battery now I have control. I'm much happier.
WAA
Great app
Great Good working ...excellent app love it
Great!!
Samsung galaxy S4 Its very good to knows about bettry timing and refreshing. ..
Very good
Great App
aus tlga!!
Awesome App
Great Awesome app I love it
Great Great apps
Really good Very useful and accurate
Love it Recommend
The best way for me to be able to save my batt
This battery saver is excellent
Great app This app is a great battery saver app that shows me how much percentage of charge is left and it is very easy to use
Awesome Cool
Excellent app
Pretty awesome I love this app its amazing really good much better than the last one I used
Good Very very very good
Excellent
5225 Excellent app dude.
Great Application thank you . You have made our lifes easy
Galaxy pocket It is an excellent app for my mobile
Osama Best battery booster
yes definitely the best
Its totally awesome
Nice So far is good!
great !!
Good app
Nice app... Love it...kewp it up...♡♡
Good Good
Nice suggestions
love love this app ,
Nice
Samsung Mobile Nokia phone
Great app
Wow Nice
Good
Hello sangle bro
Excellent! Great app for saving the phone battery.
Very nice app Excellent app
nice good app
awsome iam only downloading this app for bbm
Niggle For Nil
Nice Love thus apps.
Awesome No words r there to express the performance simply an great appp I ll rate it has 5
Excellent Must try for battery saving
Best app
Loved it so much It is nice to use
K Lol
Hp kangra Nyc yaar good battery saver
Best battery saver
Useful and innovative.
Works great Best battery app by far. Nice to be able to see exactly what is using up your battery also the graph showing battery life daily is nice to have. Wish more apps were as well constructed as this one! Thx!!
Useful
Amazing!
Great App This app helps me keep my battery usage under control. I can see battery usage, time left, and shows me all apps that are still open. This is the best app I have used for battery life purposes!
Loved it. Its advice on battery is good & also about other apps consumption of battery.
i I
Du battery saver Great!
عااااااالی
Nice
Du battery saver & widgets
tab 3 just loved the app
Very good and excellent. No
This is a very good apps I love it Thanks
Nice work
Ho
Sony Xperia Z2 Only just started using it but has a couple of great power saving options let's see how it works out..
Loved it Idk
Avinash shukla Very good
Nice
Ravi H RL
good
AWESOME This is the best battery saving app ever
Kool app
Nice software Tq
This Application is the Bomb
Good
Bala Nice app i thin
Adven
Very good Great way to see how much battery you have left and how to stop wasting it.
By far the best app This is by far the best app I have used for better battery backup. Recommended.
BLFMAX Grt app. Use every day.
Best applications
Works great!
Saeed
Good Good
Awesome app M love this app
good exelent work
very nyc app I like it.very useful
Very good Very useful app
Really great battery saver
Best battery saver It is the best battery saver i hv evr used....
Best app The best battery saver for android mobiles
Simple and free I think there are some things you can pay for with this app, but I've only downloaded it and it optimizes my battery usage. Helpful.
It's good
Cool Seriously nice
Nice Yeah, I love it, it saves my battery's percentage. good job.
Good It is a good program
Good Good
this has helped me a lot
Excillent
Best app Hey all..you must tried this app
Yogi ****
V good
Very nice application Very nice aaplication
Love your phone, have this.
save battery wow love it
Really good
Ho
Good Very good ba ery saver
Ok Vathiyar
Nice
DU. "poa" It's fantastic. My LG E440 has been saving much power since i installed this app,I really love it.
Oh ... Its the best saving app omg its so good to your app love it saving app to viruses and clean error from fast battery slow fill ...
Awesome app
Best
It's very cool!
Awesome!!!!! Really does work great!!!!! Thanks guys & keep up the great work:)
Quick and gives options to select.
Great app :)
This app is really good my cell phone is now save battery saver use this app its really good i love this Great
Very good It's good app to save battery
Battery Saver Great App.
Good Much bettet
Good app Good app
Ok Ok
We r veary happy from it Excellent
Amazing application.
Useful app
Battery Protector This app is very efficient in managing battery life. Congrats
Very good It is useful for battery management
great one! very helpful
Gionee p2s I love this app battery save in my phone
AMAZING. SAVES POWER AWESOMEE
Good Good
Kishan Singh Hiiiiiiii
This is good. 👍👍👍👍
G Really good app
Great app! It really does what it says Just try it out ... I think you'll like it
this has helped me a lot
Its awesome app
I like it so far
Harnarayan This is very good saver.
Great It is so amazing my phone used to loose charge so fast but now it doesn't
Nice
Love it It helps soo much
Awsm....
Awsome!!!!!!!!!!
Terbaik Very good application
Good
Great Recomand
ok its just ok
Big D Awesome
DU Battery Saver Nice clean visuals are somehow gratifying when you used to shut down all the battery draining background Crap. Nice app!
so better awesome app
Excellent Nice and best app to save charging in smart phones
ILoveit! It's great <3
gud
This is what i need Exelent
It was great love it
Kelly Very good
Great app Has extended my battery life considerably. I had 54% remaining after 14 hours from charge with light use. Plus great widgets.
Request More app like " cooling device" for improvement for any device specialy slow,logs,virus, but now its great keep it up ..... good bless
Impressive ...
Good apps
I like it really much I like it really much
Du battery Works
Cool app
SHARUK KHAN I like this app so much it a wonderful app
that not my picture man
Jr Jr
I will try you..
Khali naam bolo
I will see how it works hope it works good
Samsung S5 Oh gosh. Super powerful battery app. Thanks adcoms. More power.
Battery Saver
Way Way The Love Of My Life Rip Let's make a change in life, because I have God on my side Thank You Jesus. Can we get an amen !!!!!!
من همش رو نصب کردم از این بهتر نمیشه خیلی خوبه
i like it :-)
Save battery life
I give u five star
Save battery llfe Need so know went charge it . precent charge. Hope fix my battery.
Good
Excellent Excellent
Saving battery life Very good
More work We use more time use due to mobile charge really it is very good apps
Beta Good
Nice Nice appa
"Cool app."
Nice Nice
Lasting
Very useful. Fine.
Love It
Creat Good
Good
Batery saving Good job
App Nice
SumA Kasjk
like
Awesom
Good
Kanchan Test this app now
This battery is ver good
It is better than other apps
Who wants to know Long tall and black
Gud app to save mobile battery
Goody Helpfully
Nice app
Nice app
Save battery life Helps to keep battery from going to fast and performance
Good app
It's nice
Save battery Apps
Nice app
It's OK I like it app
Good app Good use worth downloading it
New User
Don't no yet cus I av not asset it on my phone.
Save battery life Its ok.three stars.like when charged it sounds tone to let you know its ready.this app dont shut runnin apps in background.
Nice one No sound
No don't instal Very time westeing
Really nice great BIG ADD. Where's the app? All I seen was the add nothing at all of this app Sorry deleted it.
The ad is too large. Uninstalled in a second.
My phone dies even faster I that it was a good app but no😤
Poor
Ad machine Save your time and battery. Do not install!
Stupid
Crap All ways covers in adds
Unsophisticated!
Thanks for all
This app didint work my phone died right away
Antivirus Facebook
Nice
Great program! It works quite well on my Samsung Galaxy S6 Edge plus
Greeeat App and I like it 😍
Battery doctor Awesome
Good It's okey
Docs orders App tells you whats wrong and fixes it.
Awesome! Really works
Awesome
Nice to use
Okey la Baru guna ja. Harap2 membantu
Good Ok
So far so good.
Outstanding!!! Dont know how I would survive without it:-D:-D:-):-)
YST Manage my phone's battery so much better
Better than other battery saver Thank you battery doctor. Working in my galaxy star gts 5282
Amazing app
Good app but... It does great except sometimes it will shut off your email sync and it can be confusing to figure out how to turn it back on the first time it happens had to chase a lot of Google leads
Very... Very good
Excellent It actually does what it says. . . perfectly
Awsome app on my phone its perfect but the availability on tablet devices must be fixed
Extended nabi xd from 9 hours to 11hours. Great
Good Very good
Nice Good
Charging Good.
Cool Great
A+ A+
Im come back now i can use it but Please improve this app...hope now I'm enjoy to use this app.
Like it &lt;3
Mp Good..
Iloveit so much
Good :)
Great app Very usefull
Exelent
Amazingly Functional! Best battery saving app I've tried. Super easy to use.
Great app This app is a great way to keep you battery in excellent health. Thanks Devs.
Good
Very useful...
U guys nailed it...! The best battery saver app.. keep it up cheetah mobile !!
Useful
Supet Vety nice and useful application
Great app...... however This app works awesomely however it would be even more awesome if you guys could make it to where the app could be moved to SD..... if not it is still a great app
Works well.
Bless
Sambar jaffa Sambar. Sollu ra.
Doctor. Battery. Is.the best You fix the battery on my phhone
:-)
very nice!good!well done!!e
Awsome
Great app ... !!!!
Killer app Works for my new LG
Juk Hmmnn so nice
Nice and very good app
It's amazing...
Best app It is awesome
Excellent Does what it says
Battery saver
Great app Working perfect thank you
sipp
Battery doctor Just lovely
Good Good app
Very nice
دکتر باطری عالیه واقعا لازمه ممنون
Battery Doctor I find this app very helpful. I love it.
Goood Kalo einai oxi tipt trelo
Loved it Awesome app
I like it nice working software
JITEN THIS IS NO1 APP IN THE WORLD
Awesome! So easy-to-use
Eo Nicee
Nice power saver Using it and finding it extremely helpful from keeping my check on the draining of my battery. ..5 stars deserved.
Nice Very effective
Abdul Kader Siddik Good app
It is really a doctor Good
Mohammed t Top app
Ok Good
Great app! Can't live without it.
I love it... I love it....
Helped my phone battery
Very useful tool Thanks
Love it
Great I like it
It's worth the 5 stars, this is an app i cant live without. Love it!
battery doctor Loving it
Seriously Best app I recomend this app . I'm in love with it. ..
Great Great to
Works Awsomely
No problems perfect app for my phone
Awesome Awesome
Good mixed bag Helps me keep my phone running by deleting or restricting applications. Unfortunately it is one of the applications that slow the phone down. On balance it really helps but I wish the app was more efficient.
Awsome A fantastic app that works!!
Ok
Good one
Excellent It does what it says on the tin. Great Little free app saving battery life. Best thing its a freebie but would buy this app.
This app has been great to be able to instantly shut down everything that I didn't even know was running and extend my battery throughout the day.
Great Works fantastic! !! No problems at all
Very good!!!
It's great app
So far so good ill see just dOwnload it
Great Keeps my battery safe and running longer love it
More battery life is so much better thank you
Love it
Great app. Extended my already awesome battery life on my new droid razr maxx.
An extra and more thorough charge for your phone It's great..so far. I like the three stage charge...however, even though it seems to be pic perfect, the only thing i have to complain about is the fact that this app itself burns CRAZY ENERGY and it freezes it cuts off but at least you know what it its
Can't be faulted
Great app! I would like to recommend this to all of those who need longer battery life. It really works.
Good
kool nice
Great app to use
Yeah very helpful!!!
Grt aap
Save your phone's battery
LOVE IT!!!!! It has helped my phone so much... before I got this app my phone would not take charge past 50% if that. And now that I have it my phone has a full charge. And phone acts way better!!!!!
Nice Good
Good job!
Life saver!!! I love this app! I have tried many apps that say they can help with battery life but none do so like this one! Extends my battery lifex2!!! Recomend this one for sure!!
It helps you so your phone wont go dead
Etetets Duh :(
This is the best free app I have used. The updates keep the app always fresh love it.. Thanks
F9
Nice V.........Nice
One of the best apps Very useful app...one of the best apps out there.
Like Like
Love it It helps save your battery a lot
superb i like this app so much. five stars!!
Great app Saved me 5 hours
Thanks
Saves p owerr Thx B
App Helped My Phone Out Tremendously
Great Realy great
Nice app I like this application and I'm very happy with it
Great Really works well.
Battery Yall giving me more batterty instead of what i usually have thankyou!!!
Powerful battery app I love it
The one which I want Just 3 words for it Amazing Excellent Un belivable So easy to use and so power saver I love it
Best App in the world♡♡♡ Awesome.... Everyone should have this app in mobile.. this is one of the best app I have ever seen ♥♥♥♥
It works well surprisingly. So here is 5 stars for being worth the download.
Yaaay It helps so much
Goodjob Nice
nice one
Ashish Excellent app
Satisfyed Best power saver ever , optimizes run signifiantly ! Well worth the app.
battery doctor is terrific!
The best Good app
Ok
Great app.
Good Good super
It good
Great app Nice battery saver app
Mr birow Battery doctor.awsome
Best battary saver I've used lots of battary saver but it is best battary saver
Doing good with me so far.....like it
Great app highly recommend Does what it says it will do, and so much more.
Top rate app! Use this app every time I need to charge my battery, stops me overcharging!
Nice app,good job👏
Thank you guis soooooo mush !
Great app! Works like gangbusters!
Very impressive new version. Good & useful app for all mobile users.
Prince Nice app
Great app Love this app. User friendly. Have recommend this to friends
Good
Great app for battery life extension Great app, but like some other complaints the widget is slow to update.
Excellent app Very useful for monitoring the charging of your battery
Very helpful to save battery
Great Works well
Great ap Easy to use
Extra ordinary
Great app to extend your battery life!
Battery Doctor An Excellent App Just Great!!! Really gets the job done, and nicely too!!!¡¡¡¥ Try it Now, you can do it!!! :-);»°)
Excellent !
Good
Nice app
Battery Saver It works. Must have.
Sf Fog L
Nice work. Phone used to die every 3-4 hours before I got this app. Now my phone can go 12-14 hours before I have to charge it. I'm very happy with this app.
Excellent app
Excellent Excellent
Fab app Does exactly what it says it does :-D superb!
Great app Great app!
I can't imagine my phone without this app!
Battery Doctor
Nice Coooooooool
Nice
Amazon This app is great !! You dont know what your phone keeps running for no reason but this tells me an i can shut it down an increase my battery time !!! Love it ....5 STARS no doubt !!!!!
Good app
Lg ZTE Its really good really helps.
Thank Love nd like it
Its super
Nice app
So far so good
Love it Works great
Works great so far
Huat ah
Awesome saves battery makes all my apps faster awesome keep it up!!
lovuuu7 NSP vccee
Its Good
Battery saver
Yes Yes
Good Application Best software in android apps
Great
So gud Ut helps alt
very nice aap ...
Extremely helpful!!
Excellent application Good job make it more effective and fix the all problems
Good Good power saver
Grt app.
Good battery saver I love it. I wish I could have downloaded early
App Excellent app to be installed
Awsome This app is one of the best app that will help a lot
Works I've noticed a difference in my battery life. Not bad, not bad at all.
I love it
Love it
Ok
Awesome app
Good This app is excellent
H Like
The best or nothing Perfect software by "ks mobil"
Tab 3 Works great.
Best Best app to extend your phones battery life
S 5 Works fine so far.
Excellent app
Battery doctor Works really well...wish I would've gotten it sooner...this really works soo good...thanks!!!
Loved it Nice app.
Battrry doctor Its good on my samsung tab....
Nice app.....Nd wonderfull too
Good
Hope its fined
battery dr. its a very niceee app
battery docter nice app.
Battery dr
I am satisfied with the improvement.
Battery. Doctor A great application love that it even cleans
Battery Doctor My S4 loves this app. Very easy to employ, it does ALL the work while you "manage" the app.
Nice
Wonderful
Golden Awesome App!!!
excellent now i have 80% after 24hrs
I hate it! It kick me out when I go to save power!
Awsome Love itt
Goog like
Dan Maupin Love it!
Great saver
East to use Works well very happy
Great So useful power app.
Verry good apps
Great app thanks a lot
Great Works fantastic
Cool app Great
This is so good please install this app
Really Helps A true lifesaver application. I use it almost daily to keep phone and tablet humming.
Nice
Battery Loved it
Urban Jrjr
Best Superb
Nice
Nice
It really helps .superb app.
App This really works
The best yet I've tried all battery savers an used them to the fullest had to charge twice a day then put in battery dr an mt battery last all day thanks to the widget wen ur done push task killer n it adds more time an also tells u how many min left on battery more accurate wants its going for a couple days too know u n ur phone n full protection my battery now only needs it wen going to bed u can also put the hours not to b woke up while phn on
Awseome Its really working
Buena Application
Super appp
best great App
Very good
Nice
battery dr. its a very niceee app
Great app !
Perfect. Love it, love it........
İs good Optimizes and keeps battery in good aligned.
Battery longer Great
fvng
Wow Wow
Great Good one..
Good Like it
Lovely Brilliant
Great app!! Love the app
Fast charge Charges fast
Life saver! Saves me from charging every 5hours. Brilliant!
Loved it I like this app because of it save the battery and i advice u to install the app this is greaaaaaàatttttttttttttttt
what a great one!!! use this app is more better than every battery saver, love it!
good love it
★★★★★
Better than last. I like the latest interface. Easy to use and to monitor.
Great app Easy to use and understand keep up the good work
Good so far Makes closing apps easy.
Thanx easy to understand and navigate
WOW my phone keept running but now it dosent thx to this app
Lokesh Long battry
Battery doctor No issues yet it seems to save on my battery nd that's what I needed. Alls I can say is try it!
Nice!
Nice Love this phone now
Great
Good app. Good App
Cool Thanks!
Ya Best app ever
Great app
Outstanding App
Amazing
Thanks
Super
Great app.
Thanks It's save my phone I love it
Oh good Works perfect love this app download it its recomended by me works guarenteed
excelen app it realy extend my battery life.. gret app,it realy save some power,now my battery last two and a half day....
Wonderful Wonderful
Best app Works so good
Mortero Powerful
I like it
Great app
Get it, and don't regret it. Even if I had to pay a dollar I still would. This app is flawless. Saved my butt so many times on low charge.
Excellent...you must use it.
Great app Really works in terms of saving my battery. Great features too.
Great app Needs more choices what to do to clean ur phone
nice... apps
Yoooo... Goooo
Good
Great Nice
Great app
Awsome
Ks mobile apps r all good Great app as expected from ks mobile
Love it!! I get more battery life for a longer time period when I am away from home.
BATTERY SAVER... So Far, So Good. ..
Very useful Great app very useful and made my phone more efficient. Only one thing is I don't know if the power models are correct for my nexus 4
Easy to understand Really works well increases battery use by hours
Great Always love this application..it makes my smartphone works well..thank you
Perfect After trying 10 to 15 apps this is the best
Battery doctor Superb
Exllent
Battery. Doctor This app does almost everything for you.really great,SAVES ALOT OF TIME.
Cool Thanks!
Great This app just works. Period.
I love it.
U h Gt u
Amazing Download it
good app
Great app,lets me know when I have allot of apps running that burns ny battery life
Very good Thank you